Arch Oboler Collection
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Series 2. Film, circa 1925-1985, 31 linear feet (74 boxes)
  - Domo Arigato, circa 1965-1976 and undated
    - Production, filming, 1967-1976
      - Blueprint for projector prism support assembly, 1967 March 31 (Box OS 1, Folder 5)
      - Oboler notes, Japan, 1972 June-August (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Music cues, 1972 December (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Oboler personal, "Arigato shooting and cutting scripts," 1972 (Box 76, Folder 3-5)
      - S.V. inserts "Arigato," 1972 September-October (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Oboler cutting room paperwork, 1972 November-1973 January (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Cutting index, undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Cutting script, circa 1972 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Domo Arigato (Honeymoon) production board, undated (Box OS 4)
      - Optics, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Optical orders, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Sound and codebook, 1972 July-November (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Sound FX notes, wild line notes, circa 1972-1973 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Audio effects, 1972 December (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Bills paid, Japan Travel Center, 1972 June-October (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Cam. and sound reports, 1972 July-August (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - C.F.I. - "Arigato," 1972-1976 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Code book, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Filming script and notes, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Kokuyo notebook, 1972 July (Box 78, Folder 1)
        Photo scrapbook of Kyoto.
      - Music, 1972-1973 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Producers' Sound Service, 1972 December-1973 January (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Reels 1-8 dubbing logs, undated (Box 78, Folder 5-12)
      - Ryder Sound Services, Inc., 1973 March (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Synchrofilm, 1972-1973 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Scripts, 1972-1973 and undated
      - Wild lines, etc., 1972-1973 (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Arigato: A Motion Picture for Space-Vision, undated (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Arch Oboler, 1972-1973 (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - Revised pages script, undated (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - "Honeymoon: A Motion Picture for Space-Vision," circa 1972 and undated
        The original title of Domo Arigato was Honeymoon.
        - undated (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
        - Obsolete, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
        - "Honeymoon" ('Arigato')," undated (Box 79, Folder 4)
        - "Honeymoon" script, circa 1972 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Lou Sher correspondence, 1971-1974
      - 1972-1973 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Sher, Sherpix, 1972, 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Returned from Sher's files, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Five, circa 1948-1984 (bulk 1948-1952)
    Released: 1951. Production company: Lobo Productions. Distribution company: Columbia Pictures Corp. Director: Arch Oboler. Producer: Arch Oboler. Writer: Arch Oboler. Cast includes: William Phipps (Michael Rogin); Susan Douglas (Roseanne); James Anderson (Eric). Photography: Louis Clyde Stouman. Plot: The only five people to survive a nuclear holocaust try to survive in a rural area near New York City. Ultimately the group is reduced by conflict, radiation sickness, and murder to just a man and a woman.
    Notes: Filmed in 1950 on a low budget, Five was shot mainly in and around "Cliff House," the futuristic house that Frank Lloyd Wright designed for Oboler and his wife in the Santa Monica Mountains. The film was nominated for best-written American low-budget movie by the Screen Writers Guild in 1952.
    Among the correspondence with cast and crew are items concerning lawsuits filed by Oboler and a cameraman, Arthur Swerdloff, over a scuffle on the movie set. A disagreement between Oboler and Columbia Pictures over the pairing of Five with the controversial film M in theaters is also documented.
    - Cast and crew, 1948-1951
      - Actors, correspondence, 1948 November-1951 December (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Gena Gilbert photographs, circa 1951 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Only Woman employees, 1950 June-1951 January (Box 80, Folder 3-4)
    - Distribution, promotion, and publicity, 1950-1984
      - Columbia Pictures, 1951 February-1952 May (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
      - Dutch movie poster and Columbia Pictures advertisements, undated (Box OS 1, Folder 6)
      - 1951 July-1952 January (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1951 April-1959 June (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Premiere, Los Angeles, 1951 August-1952 March (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Pre-sale publicity, 1950 November-1952 January (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Advertisements for The World, The Flesh and the Devil, and Night of the Comet, 1984 October and undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Program from Screen Writer's Guild Fourth Annual Awards, 1952 February 25 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Financial, 1949-1955
      - Bookkeeping for Last Woman, 1950 July-1952 May (Box 81, Folder 7-8)
      - Bookkeeping for Five, 1950 May-1954 April (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Investors, 1950 May-1955 May (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Post-distribution receipts, 1951 March, December (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Motion picture rights agreement, 1950 July (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Only Woman budgets, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Only Woman contracts, 1949 November-1951 April (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Release of mortgage, 1951 March (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Possible investors, 1949 May-1952 June (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Legal and lawsuits, 1950-1952 February
      - Arthur Swerdloff, 1950 June-1952 February (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Production, filming, 1949-1952
      - Camera reports -- CFI, Armistead, 1950 July-August (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Camera reports, editing sheets, breakdown of film, 1950 July-October (Box 83, Folder 2-3)
      - Miscellaneous business, 1949 February-1951 June (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Sound sheets and dubbing sheets, 1950 July-December (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Music cues, circa 1950 (Box 83, Folder 6-7)
      - Music notes, 1950 September-1952 August (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Negatives, undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Only Woman props & miscellaneous for shooting, 1950 August (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Scripts, circa 1950 and undated
      - Only Woman (An Original Screenplay) by Arch Oboler, M-7C, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Only Woman (An Original Screenplay) by Arch Oboler, R-2, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Only Woman (synopsis) by Arch Oboler, undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Shooting script, Five, circa 1950 (Box 84, Folder 7-9)
      - Shooting script, circa 1950, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 85-86, Box 85, Box 86)
      - Unused scenes, shooting script, circa 1950 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - 1 + 1 (Exploring the Kinsey Reports), circa 1935-1967 (bulk 1958-1961)
    Alternate titles: One Plus One; Arch Oboler's 1+1: Exploring the Kinsey Reports; 1+1; Exploring the Kinsey Reports. Released: 1961. Production company: Fluorite, Ltd. Distribution company: Selected Films. Director: Arch Oboler; assistant directors: Richard Dixon, Gordon Milligan. Producer: Arch Oboler; associate producer, Suzanne Warner. Writer: Arch Oboler; based on his play Mrs. Kingsley's Report, which was broadcast as episode 4 of the television series Arch Oboler's Comedy Theater, 1949. Cast includes: Leo G. Carroll (Prof. R.D. Logan); Hilda Brawner (Clare Hollister); William Traylor (Hollister). Photography: George Jacobson. Plot: Consists of five stories about marriage and divorce, premarital and extramarital sexual relations, and abortion told by students in Prof. R.D. Logan's symposium on marriage and the Kinsey Reports. The stories include "Honeymoon," "Homecoming," "The Divorcee," "Average Man," and "Baby." No one in the symposium, however, discusses love.
    Notes: Includes an animated sequence by Pictafilm about a polygamous dinosaur. The film was shot in Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1960-1961.
    The materials document the challenges faced by Oboler in making a film in Canada, including hiring cast and dealing with unions and taxation issues. Oboler and his assistant Jerry Kay conducted a major publicity campaign for the film, and their promotional endeavors are well described in this group of material. There is a large quantity of financial paperwork in the collection. Also of interest is correspondence with the Kinsey Institute concerning the use of Alfred Kinsey's name in the film's title. Papers indicate that Oboler's request to use the name was initially denied, but permission may eventually have been secured since the film is sometimes subtitled, "Exploring the Kinsey Reports."
    - Cast and crew, 1935-1965
      - Book photographs, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Casting, 1960-1961 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Cast publicity photographs, circa 1961 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Actors and actresses, principally Canadian, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Actors, miscellaneous, 1960 November-1963 April (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Actors' contracts, 1960 December-1961 December (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Actors, New York,, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Bills paid, actors, 1960 December-1961 February (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Bills paid, crew, 1960 November-1961 January (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Brian Adams, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Canadian addresses, 1935 July-1965 August (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Crew time cards, 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 1-6)
      - Crew, miscellaneous, 1960 November-1962 March (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - George Golden, 1961 February (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Unions, 1961 March (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Unidentified actress, undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Unions, 1957 March-1961 March (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Contracts, 1960-1967
      - Nat Taylor, 1960 September-1961 September (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Release forms, music, etc., 1960 December-1967 June (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Selected contracts, 1961 June-September (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Distribution, 1952-1967
      - Distribution & play dates, 1952 December-1964 October (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Selected accounting, 1962 January-1964 December (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - Selected Films, Inc., 1961 June-1963 December, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 89-90, Box 89, Box 90)
      - Costs, George Schaefer, 1961 May-1962 February (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - George Schaefer and correspondence, 1952 November-1967 July (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1959-1967
      - Bookkeeping follow-up, 1960 November-1967 October (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Gross receipts, 1961 August-October (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Investors, 1960 July-1967 November (Box 90, Folder 7-8)
      - Lee Moselle regarding property contract, 1960 November-1961 February (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous accounting breakdown, 1960 November-1961 June (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Tapes and Swiss Corp., 1960 September-1963 July (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Bills paid, 1961 November (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Bills paid, editing, office, and camera equipment, 1960 December-1961 June (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Bills paid, miscellaneous Fluorite hair and props, airlines, 1960 November-1961 April (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Contracts, Sundel Frank, 1959 April-1961 December (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Copies of bills paid, 1960 November-1961 September (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Final accounting, 1960 November-1961 July (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Flourite, miscellaneous bills paid, 1960 May-1962 March (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Flourite Ltd. check stubs, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 4-6)
      - Fluorite Ltd., 1960 December-1961 February (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Old U.S. union scale book, circa 1961, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 92-93, Box 92, Box 93)
      - Budget, 1959 February-1960 December (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Lee Moselle, investors, 1960 September-1966 May (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Taxes, 1961 March (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Sales tax information (S 40429), 1961 January-April (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Legal, 1958-1963
      - Copyright correspondence, F.F., 1961 June-August (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Kinsey legal correspondence, 1958 July-1963 February (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1953-1966
      - Book, 1961 June-October (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Book follow-up, 1961 September (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - Book photographs, draft manuscript, circa 1961 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960 September-1961 September (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960 November-1966 July (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Research and material, 1953 August, 1958 March-May (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Synopsis and notes, 1953-1960 March (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Preview letters, 1961 July (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Shorthand notebooks, undated (Box 94, Folder 4-6)
      - Shorthand notebook, Eleanor Oboler, 1961 March 3 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - To do on Monday, December 12, 1960 December (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Untitled Jerry Kay notebook, circa 1960 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Production and filming, 1956-1963
      - Cutting notes, 1961 March-May (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Camera reports, 1960 December-1961 January (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
      - Cartoon — Wms + Hill, 1961 February-June (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Consolidated & Ryder, 1960 December-1961 June (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Customs follow-up, 1961 February-April (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Immigration, 1960 December-1961 April (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Insurance, 1960 November-1963 January (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Kensington Towers, 1960 December-1961 August (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Music bills paid, 1961 March-May (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Censorship, 1956 December-1960 August (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Equipment, 1960 July-1961 April (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Music, circa 1960 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Sound effects, 1960 December (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Production reports, 1960 December-1961 January (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Publicity and advertising, 1959-1963
      - Comments, 1959 April-1961 September (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Draft movie posters, undated (Box OS 1, Folder 7)
      - Movie posters and draft advertising materials, 1961, undated (Box OS 2, Folder 5)
      - Synopsis, Ivan Black c/o Jerry Franken Co., 1961 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Personal appearances, Jerry Kay, 1961 October-December, 1963 February (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Previews attendance, 1961 June-July (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Publicity, 1960 January-1961 September (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Gestchell, Franken, Black, 1961 February-1962 July (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Personal appearances, 1961 August-December (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Publicity views comments, 1961 February-1962 February (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Review quotes, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Reviews, 1961 July-1962 January (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Stories, Ivan Black, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Written public notes, 1960-1961 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Dirty pix, 1961 August-September (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Hollywood Reporter ad, 1961 August (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Los Angeles 4 Star - run, 1961 July-September (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Mike Beck, 1961 October-November (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Press book and brochure, circa 1961 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Publicity brochure, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Newpaper ads, 1961 August-October (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Radio ads, 1961 August (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Trailer (movies), 1961 August (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Television ads, 1961 August (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Advertising ideas, 1961 March-September (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Scripts, 1958-1961 and undated
      - 1+1 (A Motion Picture) by Arch Oboler, undated (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - 1+1 Exploring the Kinsey Reports (A Motion Picture) by Arch Oboler, undated, (2 folders) (Box 98-99, Box 98, Box 99)
      - 1+1 Exploring the Kinsey Reports (A Motion Picture) by Arch Oboler, old, uncorrected, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - 1+1 Exploring the Kinsey Reports (A Motion Picture) by Arch Oboler, section missing, undated (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Oboler cutting script and film editor's script, circa 1961 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
      - Dialogue continuity, 1961 October (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - October 13, 1958, 1958 October (Box 100, Folder 2-3)
      - Extra and deleted pages, 1958 September, 1959 June (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Scripts submitted, 1958 July-1960 December (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Final script, December 29, 1958, 1958 December (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Script, 1960 December (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Book, town file, undated (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
      - One Plus One: Exploring the Kinsey Reports, town file, undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - One Plus One: Exploring the Kinsey Reports, town file, 1959 May (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Movie, town file, undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Movie, town file, 1958 September (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Final script, town file, 1958 December (Box 102, Folder 3-4)
      - Final script, Oboler's final corrections, town file, undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - The Twonky, circa 1951-1985 (bulk 1951-1954)
    Released: 1953. Production company: Arch Oboler Productions, Ltd. Distribution company: United Artists Corp. Director: Arch Oboler; assistant director: Leon Chooluck. Producer: Arch Oboler; executive producer, A.D. Nast, Jr. Writer: Arch Oboler; based on the story by Henry Kuttner, published in Astounding, September 1942. Cast includes: Hans Conried (Kerry West), Billy Lynn (Coach Trout). Photography: Joseph Biroc. Special effects: Special Effects, Inc., Robert Bonnig. Plot: The Twonky is a comedy in which philosophy professor Kerry West is harrassed by the apparently sentient television that his wife has bought to keep him company while she visits her sister. When West's friend, Coach Trout, sees the television set, he calls it a "Twonky," an unexplained phenomenon. The Twonky takes over West and his home, paying West's bills with counterfeit cash, dazing visitors to the house, and even rewriting one of West's class lectures. After the Coach learns that sentient robots have been sent from the future to enforce government control on citizens, he and West try to destroy the Twonky with mixed results.
    Notes: The Twonky had only three theatrical exhibitions.
    The Twonky is the least documented of the six Oboler movies represented in the Arch Oboler Collection. There are number of 8 x 10 inch black and white photographs of actors and actresses, movies stills, and set scenes.
    - Cast and crew, undated
      - Arch Oboler Productions, staff sheet, undated (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1955
      Includes financial, production, etc.
      - 1951 June-1955 September (Box 103, Folder 2-3)
      - Correspondence for Nast file, 1951 July-1952 July (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence for Nast file, 1951 June-1952 May (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - 1951 May-1952 June (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Distribution, 1954-1985
      - Distribution slips, 1954 July-1969 March, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 103-104, Box 103, Box 104)
      - United Artists distribution statements, 1970 February-1985 February (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1951-1954 and undated
      - [Bills to be checked?], Recordex, undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Bookkeeping, 1951-1954 (Box 104, Folder 6-7)
    - Photographs, undated
      - undated (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, 8 x 10 inch, undated (Box 105, Folder 2-3)
    - Publicity, 1952-1953 and undated
      - Synopsis, undated (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Draft advertising materials, undated (Box OS 2, Folder 6)
      - Publicity, 1952 March-1953 April (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Scripts, 1951-1961 and undated
      - Final cutting script, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Final cutting script, 1961 December (Box 105, Folder 7-8)
      - 1951 (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
      - Motion picture script, circa 1951 (Box 106, Folder 3-5)
      - Movie script, town file, 1951 June (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Movie, town file, undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Series 3. Frank Lloyd Wright, Real Estate, 1940-1989, 2.5 linear feet (6 boxes)
  Architect Frank Lloyd Wright prepared residential designs that were used in construction on Oboler’s property in the Santa Monica Mountains, near Malibu, California. Oboler and Wright’s relationship was personal as well as professional, and Oboler wrote magazine articles about his experiences with Wright as well as proposed film biographies of his friend. The Frank Lloyd Wright, Real Estate series documents all of this and also includes information on Oboler’s residence, such as real estate sale offerings of the property following Oboler’s death in 1987.
  The materials retain their original file folder names and within files are generally arranged chronologically.
  - Frank Lloyd Wright biographical materials, 1957-1985
    - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1958 April-1985 May (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright material, 1977 June-July, 1979 October, and undated (Box 107, Folder 2-3)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright, Tommy Cook, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - FLLW article, '83, 1957 September-1965 November and undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright, October 87, 1965 November and undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright material, 1958 April-1983 March (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous manuscripts, 1958 September-1977 July and undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous photocopies, 1983 January and undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Reader's Digest article, 1957 September-1958 April (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright: Rebel in Concrete, 1959, 1983 January and undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Blueprints and specifications, 1954-1958
    - Shower curtain blueprint, undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Specifications: continuation residence for Arch Oboler, Frank Lloyd Wright, architect, 1954 June-1955 December and undated (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Specifications: gate cottage and stable for Arch Oboler, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Specifications: residence for Arch Oboler, undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Structural computations: continuation residence for Arch Oboler, Frank Lloyd Wright, architect, 1954 June-1958 September (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, original materials, 1940-1985
    - Agreement contractors forms (blank) as requested by Frank Lloyd Wright for Usonian House, undated (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Building correspondence, 1940 August-1955 June (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1950 through 1959, 1953 November-1965 June (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Imp. papers Frank Lloyd Wright, Arch Oboler, information, 1940 September-1967 December (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous letters, 1955 November-1985 December (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Ranch building correspondence, 1940 February-1943 September (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Report to Lafayette Design Project, 1961 October (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1960 July-1968 December (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Maps, plats, 1958-1982
    - Ranch information: land maps, etc., 1975 and undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Real estate maps, 1958 April-1982 September (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1941-1980
    - Bills paid: Alfred Coleman Rocks (ranch) new house, 1954 May-1963 February (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Bills paid: old ranch building, 1941 March-1944 July (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Gatehouse: bills paid, 1945 December-1952 May (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - National Park Service land acquisition papers, 1978 June-1980 January (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Real estate sales, 1941-1989
    - Appraisal of real property: 33246 Mulholland Highway, 1988 August (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Arch Oboler's "Go to Hell" spiral notebook, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 10)